False
wallstreetbets
POST TITLE: GME Institutions Hold 177% of Float Why the Squeeze is not Squoze

177% of float is one thing but 142% of outstanding shares, what the fuck. And that's not even accounting for retail investors.
This is what we want guys.

Good DD with some numbers to back it up.

Don't start threads about 'Who is HOLDING'.

If there is still a play on GME then let everyone decide on their on to jump on. We don't want GME Fatigue to ruin it.

Thanks OP

Position: 150 shares.

Not financial advice.
Finally some DD with some old looking computer screens, you can always trust these
 Dont forget to ensure your shares are not being lent out as well. Please call your broker to confirm. I thought mine with Etrade were not. Turns out if you have margin enabled they can and will be. Only way to get my shares back was to disable margin.  
Make sure your shares are not being lent out!
Thank you for this. Regardless of what peopleÆs look is about GME or not. It was the original members of WSB that started the hype which caused everyone to flood in. So I have to believe that they are still holding regardless of whatÆs happening on this sub. Hopefully this doesnÆt get deleted and people can see it for what it is. Good post OP, but youÆre late for your shift at WendyÆs.
HFs hate this man
The inside look at Bloomberg terminal gave me a ??
Good post man, we need more of this.
A second squeeze will happen. Hedge Funds ainÆt gonna take a $19 billion haircut and not fight back. However, this fight is between hedge funds, not retail. My advice for those underwater and bag holding, when it starts, whatever your breakeven, please either get out or buy puts immediately you are either at or slightly above you break even. Principal investment safe, then if it starts to tear above 500, just watch the charts like a hawk, and hit the sell order, once you get to the price you want to let go.
Next week, will be interesting.

Good luck and stay safe.
As a ??? that is holding until the squeeze or bust, I love DD posts like this. Not because it convinced me to hold (since IÆm holding regardless) but because it gives me more confidence and reassurance that thereÆs still hope and a chance of this long shot happening. Diamond handed tard till the end
????

POS: 6 shares @ACB 223
It's like 4chan found a fancy Bloomberg terminal.
All this seems very strange to me. Why put themselves further into the hole? Did they really think they could tank the stock that much? Is this an all or nothing scenario for them?
Nice DD man, yeah this bongo still has a lot of bong to go. IÆm dead sure they didnÆt cover shit and all itÆll take is one solid catalyst
This confirms my bias! Thank you for the DD! ???
TLDR; Don't be a  ?????....?? ??? on 3/12
If youÆre bag holding, and deep in the red, your best option is not to sell. Hedge Funds are fighting each other and a squeeze is coming. It will happen within the next two months, as the FTD tactic ainÆt gonna work this time, with all the class action law suits and SEC being forced to scrutinize this saga.
Honestly the easiest thing, to blow this thing to the moon is a major investment by a retail whale, which locks up the remaining float of approximately $ 4 billion. Given CohenÆs track record, I would be shocked, if he isnÆt on the phone trying to make this deal. Not to save retail investors, but to eliminate the shorts trying to destroy, his 13% investment and it also gives him breathing space to restructure this company.
I donÆt know what the fuck is going on but all DD post are getting removed. Try r/GME
I just want an alert for when the next squeeze is coming, so I can buy beforehand.

I have no idea what IÆm doing.
Feb 9th users find out gme is still shorted x amount and flood back in, probably lands at $200ish a share is my guess.
OP I think you're more right than wrong. 

After the SEC short restriction yesterday, the price shot up 30%. I think that's because GME is so low volume that any big buy orders, without shorting via synthetic shares, is going to send the price flying. 

Low volume on a stock makes them incredibly volatile.
Did you ever hear the tragedy of Melvin Capital? I thought not. ItÆs not a story the Suits would tell you. ItÆs a WSB legend. Melvin Capital was a hedgefunds of the suits, so powerful and so wise he could use the shorts to influence the mercantile exchange to create sharesà He had such a knowledge of shorting that he could even keep the positions he invested in from liquidating. The dark side of trading is a pathway to many abilities some consider to be unnatural. He became so leveragedà the only thing he was afraid of was liquidating, which eventually, of course, he did. Unfortunately, he taught WSB everything he knew, then WSB liquidated him in his positions. Ironic. He could save others from liquidating, but not himself.
I know little of the Max Pain theory. Is it cyclical and will tend to hand around where the most OTM calls are over time, or does it rebound heavily after reaching it?

Great post! Very informative. This is the discussion that is needed, not endless memes at a time like this.
I got ?? but THE date gets pushed back anf back and back and back and back
More ELI5 version of how more than 100% of shares can be floated.

Alice has 10 shares of GME and wants to hold. Bobby wants to short GME, so he borrows AliceÆs shares and sells them to Carol. 10 shares shorted, right? Carol doesnÆt know she bought shorted shares, and David comes along and wants to short GME as well. David borrows CarolÆs shares and sells them to Ezekiel. Now those 10 shares are shorted 20 times. 200%.
I think what's going on with $GME is still interesting:

  


\- Why was there no Shelf Offering? Were they afraid of damaging their reputation?

\- That +100% spike Friday morning with huge volume  


  


I guess is the spike on Friday was simply a HF closing it's position, because by now a Ryan Cohen turnover is already priced in and in that case, price will unlikely fall below $50 with the current hype.

  


But why weren't they covering over the span of a day, but instead pay extra to pump the price? This is most probably the HFs backstabbing each other. And I think we will see more of this in the next days.

  


All shorts want to close their positions eventually and probably before (1) other shorts do, (2) Ryan Cohen makes a move, (3) index rebalancing pumps the price even more. Time is again ticking for the shorters (doesn't matter of they shorted at $4 or $420).

  


So why was there no Shelf Offering? This is where institutional ownership becomes important again. Institutional ownership is over 100%, which means the shares sold by the shorters are locked in ETFs. It's not possible for \*all\* shorts to cover, unless they beg for a shelf offering.

  


I don't think management was expecting the $GME hype. Their plan was probably from the beginning to watch HFs backstabbing each other and make a shelf offering at the end. And this process is still going.
It's interesting to wonder what the next catalyst could be (if we get one). Probably a firm trying to fuck over another firm
Solid DD

Meet me at the back of WendyÆs.
Where'd I leave my hopium pipe...
Everyone clowned DFV for buying GME to begin with, then it spiked. Everyone is clowning those that held GME through so far, it will spike...
From looking at past squeezes (Overstock , KBIO, VW) the trend seems to be company pressure causing the squeeze. With VW, we all know it was Porsche as the majority owner. With KBIO, Martin did it twice in a short span, with Overstock it was the company shifting to their own token and recalling shares. 

Until that happens for Gamestop, does retail have the actual power to squeeze? From everything I've read and understood, we have so far only experienced gamma squeezes. And with trade restrictions handicapping retail, its given shorts undue advantage to keep dodging the pressure to cover fully. Until then, they can continue to manipulate the market and extend their lifelines. Obviously a reason for us to ??.

But we need the trigger. I wonder if that's why Gamestop hasn't made their move yet. Perhaps they're waiting to better understand the layout before doing so. If and when they do anything to recall shares , that's the major trigger for shorts to have to cover. 

Thoughts?
Thx
I like
I'm with you. 

20@ 118
Hey FUD boys go eat a fat dick
But why is the shorts cost to borrow so low?
Thanks man. That was actually good to read some well thought out and sourced DD.
Holding till 10000 a share
Keep requesting the emergency shareholder meeting and the reverse split. Fuck them out of all their short positions
Yes this is exactly what has likely happened.  Shorts took on synthetic long positions as the stock fell to make it look like they covered and hedge deltas.

There are also clearly too many shares outstanding, but I'm not sure that technically needs to be resolved yet.  A reverse split or special dividend would require reconciliation I'd imagine - but normally share count mismatches don't really matter as long as you get your money when you place a sell order in your brokerage.
Do we really need short float/interest numbers, when we can easily look up how much institutions own? That number tells us there is a fuck ton of shares shorted. GME will rise again ????
DonÆt do this me! You going to make me go balls deep again, Jesus Christ!!
OP float doesn't mean outstanding shares. So having more than a float is perfectly normal. But 177% figure is still interesting. That means most of the retail liquidity is absorbed by institutions.
So stop buying and selling,

###**LET THEM SQUEEZE EACH OTHER**

**APE HOLD TILL 963.99**

###THIS IS FOR INFORMATIONAL PURPOSES ONLY; EVERYTHING I WRITE IN REDDIT IS NOT IN ANYWAY, LEGAL, TAX, OR FINANCIAL ADVICE?
Just because there hasnt been a squreze yet doesnt mean itll never happen. They are just dragging this out long as possible to shake the weaklings into selling. 

HOLD THE LINE. BUY THE DIP. 


THIS ISNT OVER 

Im going to be PAID by my bday 3/14.....

?????????????????????????????????
I guess we will find out Tuesday. I do feel stupid for not pulling out gains as we went to 480+. But IÆm still positive overall. Hope this works out!
I keep looking at the daily short volume reported by FINRA. Every day this week has has a ratio over 50% of shares through NYSE and NASDAQ.

FridayÆs volume was 19M sold short of 34.5M total volume for a ratio of 55%

http://regsho.finra.org/regsho-Index.html

GME is still heavily shorted
Game on!  This is gonna be a process.
 

very interesting how mods keep removing these posts. all the upvoted posts are about memes, other stocks, or gme gain porn like everyone has sold. IMO most people are still holding on to GME, stuff like this is what should be upvoted and I'm not sure why it keeps getting removed. Just remember its only been a week and most big players are still in.
I hope it gets to 400, everyone can pull out and at least cover their losses and we forget this whole thing ever happend. 


4.5@100
Don't care about the movement. Just want money, kittens and to go fishing.
Guys let's keep things realistic here. Nothing you or I do at this point will make or break this squeeze. There's blood in the water now. There is big money out there who wants to make bigger money. And they're going to do it at the cost of Citadel and Melvin and everyone else who is short this stock.

IF this is still heavily shorted, and based on what I'm reading here it looks like it is, we should expect to see a feeding frenzy start soon. Hedge funds aren't teamed up. They're rivals. Some already made millions, others will be making billions if they can start the squeeze. And all we can do at this point is make sure we are positioned in such a way that we can get a few of the scraps as they drop to the bottom of the sea floor.
what do you do for a living that gives you access to a bloomberg terminal and are you holding a position in GME right now and will you keep holding?
Thanks for this DD, good stuff, sir.

I was wondering that on iBorrowDesk data fees are declining so does that mean also that borrowing stocks for shorts are much more affordable than it was on the beginning of the week? And that is actually playing against us as they need to pay less in between and allows them to dump share price further down?
i couldn't understand it must be a good dd
All aboard the rocket ship. ????
I dig this, makes a ton of sense.

I have one question though, something I haven't seen discussed a lot.

[https://iborrowdesk.com/report/GME](https://iborrowdesk.com/report/GME)

Yesterday (and really throughout the last week) we're seeing a sharp decline in the short borrow fee, which from what I was reading is an indication of the ability to borrow a stock.

[https://www.investopedia.com/terms/s/stock-loan-fee.asp](https://www.investopedia.com/terms/s/stock-loan-fee.asp)

&#x200B;

>How a Stock Loan Fee Works  
>  
>The stock loan fee amount depends on the difficulty of borrowing a stock  û the more difficult it is to borrow, the higher the fee. As short  sellers immediately sell the borrowed stock, the borrower must reassure  the lender by putting up collateralásuch asácash, treasuries or a letter  of credit from a U.S. bank. If the collateral is cash, the interest  paid by the stock lender on it to the borrower may offset part of the  stock loan fee.

If all indications are pointing to a low availability of shares, what can explain this decrease?
at this point it's pretty much out of our hands. Retail simply does not have the funds and/or coordination to conduct this kind of attacks and scoops the ways institutionals can. 


For all we know the Friday "attacks" were done by another institution looking to enter the market, and they use the attack to drive down the price to try and scoop out all the shares from people who fold i.e. getting themselves into a better position before they trigger the squeeze.


with the opacity of data available to retail, there's just no way to know what's really going on. It's truly a bet at this stage since without access to said data, all the theories that's been bouncing for the last few days are basically all conjecture, speculation and educated guesses.


My personal opinion is that it will eventually squeeze since it's not so easy to extricate themselves from a 140% short, especially with a stock with such a small float (and decreasing as retail buy and diamond hands) and institutions not having any real desire to sell their long positions (definitely if they didn't cash out when it was $400+, it makes zero sense for them to cash out now) - the ones who intend to cash out would have done so already (i.e. MUST Asset management who closed out their position and took their profit - https://www.marketwatch.com/story/large-gamestop-shareholder-must-asset-management-sold-off-its-stake-2021-01-28).


Just my opinion naturally - anyone who wants to buy GME should do their own DD and make their own decisions.
Hold
Thank you. Some many people are talking without backing up what they say with graphs so this is some much needed insight. 

Take my free award i got.
TLDR for the apes; DIAMOND HANDS!
I've seen plenty of people on here recommending puts because they think the price will go down to $20. I don't think it's too unreasonable to think some big money has shorted at "lower" price levels too.

I don't imagine it will squeeze like the first time but there is a lot of potential for squeezing and that's why I'm holding for now.
Red 10 checking in.  8 shares.
Does anyone have some reliable sauce that Burry not only got his shares back he requested from shorters but also cashed out? He deleted his tweet calling out funds for not giving his shares back. But that's the last I saw
ItÆs like 4chan gained access to a Bloomberg terminal
It's happening !
Sold half to secure my gains, holding the other half to see what happens. I'm excited for this week!
One fact to keep in mind: Retail makes up only a single digit % of trades regularily.

The question is if there are other big companies who want a squeeze to happen.

Yes, a big event could lead to a lot of buying, but even in the previous pump retail transactions pretty much negated themselves.

If we look at searches, [interest in gamestop also declines](https://trends.google.com/trends/explore?date=now%207-d&geo=US&q=gamestop).  
To me, this is more like looking at a power play between the Hedgies.
Honestly driving the stock down this much may have just made people more resilient to hold. If you go from $300 to $60 why not just hold it?
While I'm a believer, for every post I see saying this, there are many others saying the complete opposite. 

For my own sanity, I'm going to go on a WSB hiatus until I get a clearer picture as to what's actually going to happen with this stock.

I overleveraged myself. I need to educate myself and move on.
You ever thought that the price going from 20 to 400 was the squeeze and that they closed their shorts and opened new ones at a much higher price?
RemindMe! 1 weeks
> Max pain theory states it is in the market maker's best interest (those who write options aka theta gang) for price to gravitate towards max pain, as the strike price with the most open contracts including puts and calls would cause financial losses for the largest number of option holders at expiration.

Can someone dumb this down for me?
WhatÆs the annual cost for Bloomberg terminal access? The information advantage there is pretty remarkable. Their website has it priced at ContactUs which sounds out at reach for my modestly sized portfolio.
 \[long pause while he processes what he's heard\] **So you**'re **telling me there's** a **chance**. YEAH!
??????????????? ... thatÆs how you do it right?
Idk IÆm a monkey but Max Payne 3 was pretty good so IÆll hodl ???
Guess I'm buying 1000 more shares this week.
YOU BETTER NOT BE FUCKING LYING OP. I was theorizing this shit and it's insane to see it confirmed.
Spent all my money on GME. IÆd rather be rich and retarded than poor and smart with a small loss of my investment .
So what you are saying is HOLD THE FUCKING LINE!!
So it really is like if 4chan found a Bloomberg terminal. ??
Get it to $1000 apes! We can do this, together!!
If the squeeze could be sqozed how many squeezes would the squezer sqwoze
From the little I understand of this, it proves these guys are nuts.

Remember, these guys are stoopid rich, making money is a GAME, ego's and cock waving.

They are SO pissed off, they will NOT lose to you fuckers for any reason....

.....unless the money dries up. 

This aint about the books, profits or losses, even legalities.

Its about EGO and WINNING at all costs, literally.

Power to the Apes. Holding.
Is this for real? I am $8k down and canÆt sleep.
That is so hilariously wrong
Those shorts came from the peak because gme was overrated. It's over dude
Short interests mean nothing, these could be shorts from $400. I would much rather look at the borrow interest which has gone down from 80% last week to 3.7% https://iborrowdesk.com/report/GME
Here is how Bernie can still win.
This is great work! Thanks!
Here I was thinking the Bloomber Terminal thing was a joke.
Has this just become a waiting game? Can counterfeit shares just be generated in perpetuity to keep punting on this until retail investors get bored and free up shares by selling?
I just did a short ladder attack on some punk kid walking across my lawn.
I been knew
Thanks for taking the time to post some numbers and decent analysis. I don't mind these posts.
Everyone just gonna breeze over the delay in institutional holding timing..
Yeah fucking excellent DD OP. It was nice and short and backed up with numbers and at the end of the day we dumbasses cant read, but we can count.

?fucking?
This is why I hold
"I HAVE A BLOOMBERG TERMINAL!"

WITNESS HIM.
We have rich ppl in this sub and nobody wants a terminal for a year? Lolll
TLDR: squeeze hasnt squoze. needs catalyst. catalyst nuke pending. when catalyst goes boom, retards on rocket go vroom. hold your shares fellow retards were going to alpha centauri ????????
Rock hard with 45 @ 300ish.
Everyday there is more info on how GME is going to moon. Hedges are panicking and people are realizing their manipulations by the min.  Diamond Hands baby!
We can't squeeze anything if people are still using robinhood and the like.
So basically the situation is exactly the same as it was before and we only lost momentum due to unexpected market wide restrictions, and if we do what we did again, we can all make another 25% or higher profit on this or at least get out of the bagholders club?

Okay, I'm down. I was gonna game Penny Stocks on RH til I recouped my Investment, but this works.
Honestly just holding until I either get a big payout or bust.  Not even stressing over this. ??
It doesn't matter because they'll cheat and manipulate their way out of this. Still holding $2000 $GME though. To the moon or to hellheim.
Got in at $50 and sold 70 shares at $350.  kept 40 shares for whatever the fuck happens with this insane story.  I just hope some of the unlucky bag holder retards can get some money back and not be depressed about this for the rest of their lives.
I bought 1 share of GME and am now living in my wifeÆs boyfriendÆs guest bedroom.
Access to Bloomberg Terminal = Big dick energy
interesting fact, Robinhood was fined 65 mil by the SEC last year for misleading customers. [https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2020-321](https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2020-321)
I don't think it's possible to short squeeze, Citadel acquired Melvin because Melvin smelled the margin call, the moment Citadel acquired them they covered that risk, other shorts probably have much better risk management. Also there is issue of likely GME public offering while company is so overvalued.

Main thing is the sheer volume being traded every single day, obviously the needed Nash equilibrium didn't take hold between investors.
So this starts to explain why GME hasn't dropped to nothing and even climbed a little bit (Hahahh a little bit being 20% in this case)  


Dam this is the DD we need around here. I wasn't planning on selling I have no problem going down to zero,but after seeing the stock go up a  bit on Friday my gut told me to buy a little more.  This DD helps explain what my gut feeling was about.  


Good stuff OP
In other words, it isnÆt over until the fat lady sings
And to everyone thinking of jumping on board please be careful - a lot of people have been financially hurt very badly because of the first round.  No one knows how this will end up.
Im happy that all the hype traders got out and are letting the real og wsb hold the line. I am still in the positive so no sweat. But it just didnt feel right. My DD says hold and so far in my life it hasnt failed me. I hold.
HODL![gif](emote|free_emotes_pack|money_face)
The only thing which will again save their a\*\*es are people too lazy to switch to a real trading account. So many people are looking for a shiny shitty app where you can just press "buy" / "sell".

Get yourself educated, it is not rocket science to enter a buy/sell orders on trading software/web interfaces provided by real brokers. Fidelity should be great in the USA from the recents posts here.

People who are too greedy to pay a little fee shooting their self in the knee because they never asked how it comes that their trades does not cost a fee.

&#x200B;

![gif](emote|free_emotes_pack|downvote)![gif](emote|free_emotes_pack|downvote)![gif](emote|free_emotes_pack|downvote)![gif](emote|free_emotes_pack|downvote)

Get a f\* real account at a f\* real borker!

&#x200B;

Advice from a retarded diamon hand - surviving trading in the market for more than 13 years - but not financial advice!
I almost hope this gets beaten down to $50 again on Monday so I can buy more before Tuesday. I bought 600 shares near $100. I think IÆd like to make it 1000 shares and let the chips fall where they may.
THIS is very valuable information, that indeed is verified and true. Please everyone ù screenshot, and SHARE if this post is taken down. In the meantime please keep it visible. 

OP: thank you for this info !!!!! ????
Are people still bag holding GME?  Lol
I will come back to this thread on Friday when GME is down another 20% if not more. You are clinging to a momentum trade that has waning momentum. A squeeze only happens when a stock is unexpectedly soaring (i.e., 2 weeks ago). There aren't enough NEW buyers who will enter and bid up the stock to initiate another squeeze, and to do so unexpectedly.
I see the Q anon effect is still going on around here lol. ôItÆs still gonna happen and hereÆs how.ö ôTrust the plan.ö
Whether you want to.hold.or not is up to you, but you cannot return 140 of something is owed.  That defies basic logic
Meh. Retail alone can't create enough demand to trigger a squeeze. Institutions can keep kicking the can down the road and no major share holders are going to recall their loaned shares for fear of looking like they're trying to manipulate the stock. A squeeze happened. Hoping for another squeeze but I'm not holding my breath. In for 18@300 and holding.
Not financial advice, just my view.
I saw a terminal. ThatÆs enough for me. You son of a bitch IÆm in
It was a squeeze when it was up above $400.

If you didn't sell then you missed your opportunity.
I imagine new hedge fund / smart money shorted in the 400s. Of course short interest looks high 

The simple fact is that all you retards no longer have the buying power to squeeze them.
Honestly still getting depressed, kinda seems like we the bag holders
5 stages of grief. I see you are at bargaining.
I there any argument you have against the calling of a shareholders vote? Would the calling back of all shares to their owners not be the catalyst we need?
This used to be an options sub. now less than 1/4 of the subscribers know what options are

:,( F
What do you guys think? Are they buying deep ITM calls to lower the SI ôsyntheticallyö?

https://twitter.com/mgould11/status/1357477145975664642

https://twitter.com/mgould11/status/1357485493215129600

https://twitter.com/mgould11/status/1357485842252484609
Buy the dips and board the ships ??????
How does the Bloomberg terminal get their information? Is it official or is it estimates?
How likely is it that this is due to discrepancies in the data?
great info, thank you for the DD
Last week as just fomo with a tiny squeeze. IÆm holding. I like the stock.
GME.... I don't want you to do it but if you announced a merger with Valve I would literally suck my wife's boyfriend's toes.

I don't do tricks for free.
Watch mods delete this post like they have been doing to all the posts on GME with good DD...
IM GOING TO A STRIP CLUB IN VEGAS TO CELEBRATE WSB HELL YEAHHHHHHHH SAPHIRE AT 11 PM IF YOURE IN THE AREA!!!!!!
Quality post and thank you
That 4@299 is biting me in the ass every day now.
How do you have access to Bloomberg and not know how the float can be over 100% owned?
Sir, this is a laundry mat. 

But in all seriousness thanks for posting some solid DD.
Gh gh gh gh gh gh Gee emm EEE
This is real good stuff. Now I'm really tempted to go for round 2.

Round one was good to good to me and my 60 GME trades 

Like for real, I may just go for round 2
Nice work man
This needs to be seen. ?

I had a feeling from beginning, media coverage, ladder attacks and overall manipulation. They would have not done this, if it was over. 

HF's and other big players are awful smart but they underestimated this shit. I still believe 1000$ is not a meme. 

* I just like the stock * 

(No rocket or diamond emojis because they are kinda cringy.)
So buy more Monday morning?
apology for poor memeglish

when were you when melvin capital dies?

i was sat at home eating crayon when vlad ring

æmelvin is killÆ

ænoÆ
The lower the price goes, the better deal on buying up all the available shares and the easier its made for retail investors eh
The smart thing for Cohen/GME to do would be to announce the *possiblity* of a ***reverse split***.  That's all it would take to make their stockholders/customers very very rich individuals.   ...And who's to say that Cohen doesnt just float the idea of a reverse split in the media?  Any little ***hint*** could cause an absolute panic in hedge funds who remember the 2016 DRYS (Dryships) short squeeze.

[DRYS... the GME before GME... a case study on reverse splits exacerbating short squeezes](https://www.thestreet.com/.amp/investing/dryships-soars-1-800-amid-epic-short-squeeze-13894736?__twitter_impression=true)
ah, my theory of institutions and other HFs buying em all back seems to be playing out just fine....just need that final catalyst....i hope it drops in the middle of the night premarket hours to send them scrambling
Why does there being an increase of shorted shares surprise anyone? If they think it's going to go back to $5 or $10 or whatever, of course they'll hold. I'm not saying they're right, but outstanding shorts left to cover is not a sign one way or the other. If anything, it is a consensus the big groups think it'll further drop.
For the first time in days, I actually start to believe their is still a possible bet to be made...
Although IÆm not really in the game anymore, it could be  worth the gamble/ risk.

Reading about the subject in local news (eu) one paper said short interest dropped to 21%. How would they be able to give such figure?! Bit weird for a financial newspaper.

Another more thrusty (imo) source was an interview with a professional trader that stated itÆs more likely to become a clash between hfÆs than hf vs retail...

Can anyone debunk this?
IÆm fuckin buying monday at open. LetÆs fuckin gooooooooo!
Also, I think all the highest prices reached by $GME were in pre-market. really weird how I was waiting for those prices to be passed during normal market hours but they never were? fucking bullshit what robinghood has done.
If you think hedge funds will be punished for illegal behavior I got some bad news. How many people went to jail when they crashed the economy in 2008? They flew private jets to get on their knees to beg for a bailout from congress. The SEC will go after some small fish on here.
Careful posting Bloomberg screenshots. It's likely a breach of contract and they will come down hard.
IÆll buy more when itÆs at 300 again
